question_data = [

        {
            "category": "Mythology",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "In Norse mythology, Thor once dressed as a woman.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Geography",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Greenland is almost as big as Africa.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Geography",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Vatican City is a country.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "American rapper Dr. Dre actually has a Ph.D. doctorate.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Science: Mathematics",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "The &#039;Squaring the Circle&#039; problem is solvable.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "In Kill La Kill, the weapon of the main protagonist is a katana. ",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "In Team Fortress 2, being disguised as a scout or medic results in a speed boost.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Scatman John&#039;s real name was John Paul Larkin.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Kiznaiver is an adaptation of a manga.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "In Heroes of the Storm, the Cursed Hollow map gimmick requires players to kill the undead to curse the enemy team.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        }
]